to foe by
making a girl
I like laughed
so hard she
ended up in
hospital and I
almost lost my
job so there's
this girl I
like at work
and we're really
good friends were
having lunch and
were making those
ironic depression mean
jokes as most
friends do for
some reason I
am I annoyingly
a stupid way
to get her
laugh got the
idea to say
well Hey you
know what's just
one letter away
from sad dad
and promptly did
the deed also
I have ability
to cry on
demand so I
just stared stone
cold her and
let to terrace
fall down she
finds it funny
extremely funny so
funny she drops
to the floor
and starts laughing
her as off
after a good
thirty seconds she
starts grabbing her
chest and coughing
I asked if
she was okay
when she starts
wheezing and begins
to convulse a
bit freaking the
fuck out and
thinking she's having
a damn seizure
I start to
reach for my
phone and in
the exact second
my manager randomly
decides to come
in and sees
this big guy
towering over this
poor little girl
on the floor
I only managed
to cut off
her impending rage
by saying I
think she's having
a seizure and
I'm calling nine
one one fortunately
I was able
to explain to
her what happened
after the ambulance
came turns out
she has asthma
and my job
caused a flare
up and was
waving her arms
to try to
tell me to
get her inhaler
whoops